Darius-Gabriel Urechiatu

Contact

Address

Dr Ioan Muresan, Timisoara

Phone

0726488536

Email

dariusgabriel52@gmail.com

Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/dariusgabriel-urechiatu-0b032119b/

Website

https://quizzicalliskov-3c6fbc.netlify.app/

GitHub

https://github.com/darius29

Additional Skills

- HTML5 junior
- CSS junior
- JavaScript junior
- ReactJs junior
- TypeScript junior
- NodeJs basic
- MySQL basic
- GraphQL basic
- Git independent user

Professional Summary

My name is Urechiatu Darius-Gabriel. I am a junior web developer. Playing football and swimming helped me develop my social abilities. I like meeting new people and making friends. I can work independently and also within a team setting.

Efficient Junior Web Developer with a bachelor's degree in informatics and 1 year of experience in challenging development environments. Excellent communication and organizational abilities with a resourceful approach to solving diverse problems. Collaborative and hardworking team player with critical thinking skills and a systematic approach.

For now, I'm interested in projects that involve web development, finding a new team with who I can practice my abilities. I'm eager to learn and striving for perfection in everything I do. Hardworking and passionate jobseeker with strong organizational skills eager to secure an entry-level environment.

Work Experience	
Sc Fluentis SRL, Timisoara Cloud	02/2020 - 03/2020
Sc Conte Human SRL WordPress Developer	04/2021 - 06/2021
Nokia Internship - Web Development	07/2021 - 11/2021

Е

Education	
West University of Timişoara Faculty of Mathematics and Informatics	09/2017 - 09/2020
"Traian Doda" National College Real profile, mathematics-informatics	09/2014 - 06/2017

01/2021 - 03/2021

The Complete Web Developer in 2021: Zero to Mastery Course

Projects

Crown Store - From Crown Clothing you can buy the latest clothing items (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React) - https://github.com/darius29/CRWN Todo app - Here is a Todo list! (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React-Hooks) https://github.com/darius29/Todo

Smart Brain - This magic brain will detect the face from your picture. Give ita try (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React) -

https://github.com/darius29/facerecognitionbrain

Robofriends - Search and find out which is your favorite robot. (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React) - https://github.com/darius29/robofriends